{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^2 + 9x + 12) / (-3x - 3)", "answer": "x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x - 3 | -3x^2 + 9x + 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(6x^3 - x^2 - 17x - 3) / (-2x - 3)", "answer": "-3x^2 + 5x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x - 3 | 6x^3 - x^2 - 17x - 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(6x^3 - x^2 - 7x + 3) / (-2x + 1)", "answer": "-3x^2 - x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x + 1 | 6x^3 - x^2 - 7x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-15x^2 + 4x + 3) / (-3x - 1)", "answer": "5x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x - 1 | -15x^2 + 4x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(15x^2 + 26x + 8) / (-3x - 4)", "answer": "-5x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x - 4 | 15x^2 + 26x + 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(3x^3 + 5x^2 + x + 6) / (x + 2)", "answer": "3x^2 - x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\nx + 2 | 3x^3 + 5x^2 + x + 6\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-2x^3 + 5x^2 - 8x + 3) / (-2x + 1)", "answer": "x^2 - 2x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x + 1 | -2x^3 + 5x^2 - 8x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-2x^2 + 15x - 25) / (2x - 5)", "answer": "-x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n2x - 5 | -2x^2 + 15x - 25\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(16x^3 - 28x^2 + 30x - 10) / (4x - 2)", "answer": "4x^2 - 5x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x - 2 | 16x^3 - 28x^2 + 30x - 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(20x^3 - 23x^2 - 9x + 6) / (-5x + 2)", "answer": "-4x^2 + 3x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-5x + 2 | 20x^3 - 23x^2 - 9x + 6\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(3x^2 + 8x + 4) / (-3x - 2)", "answer": "-x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x - 2 | 3x^2 + 8x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(16x^2 - 16x - 5) / (4x - 5)", "answer": "4x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x - 5 | 16x^2 - 16x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(16x^3 + 16x^2 - 17x + 3) / (4x - 1)", "answer": "4x^2 + 5x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x - 1 | 16x^3 + 16x^2 - 17x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^2 - x + 2) / (x + 1)", "answer": "-3x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\nx + 1 | -3x^2 - x + 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(3x^2 + 10x + 3) / (3x + 1)", "answer": "x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n3x + 1 | 3x^2 + 10x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(3x^3 + 9x^2 - 11x + 4) / (-x - 4)", "answer": "-3x^2 + 3x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x - 4 | 3x^3 + 9x^2 - 11x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(20x^3 - 4x^2 - x + 12) / (-5x - 4)", "answer": "-4x^2 + 4x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-5x - 4 | 20x^3 - 4x^2 - x + 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(16x^2 + 36x + 20) / (-4x - 5)", "answer": "-4x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-4x - 5 | 16x^2 + 36x + 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-20x^3 - 33x^2 - 20x - 4) / (-5x - 2)", "answer": "4x^2 + 5x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-5x - 2 | -20x^3 - 33x^2 - 20x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(20x^2 + 21x - 5) / (4x + 5)", "answer": "5x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x + 5 | 20x^2 + 21x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(6x^2 - 4x - 10) / (-2x - 2)", "answer": "-3x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x - 2 | 6x^2 - 4x - 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(10x^3 - 13x^2 - x + 4) / (-5x + 4)", "answer": "-2x^2 + x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-5x + 4 | 10x^3 - 13x^2 - x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^2 - 11x - 20) / (-x + 4)", "answer": "-4x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x + 4 | 4x^2 - 11x - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(x^3 + 4x^2 - 6x + 1) / (x - 1)", "answer": "x^2 + 5x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\nx - 1 | x^3 + 4x^2 - 6x + 1\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^3 + 4x^2 - 13x - 10) / (-x - 2)", "answer": "-4x^2 + 4x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x - 2 | 4x^3 + 4x^2 - 13x - 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(2x^2 - 2) / (x + 1)", "answer": "2x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\nx + 1 | 2x^2 - 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(15x^2 - 8x - 16) / (5x + 4)", "answer": "3x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x + 4 | 15x^2 - 8x - 16\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^3 + 20x^2 - 12) / (4x - 4)", "answer": "-2x^2 + 3x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x - 4 | -8x^3 + 20x^2 - 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(6x^2 + 13x - 5) / (-2x - 5)", "answer": "-3x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x - 5 | 6x^2 + 13x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^2 + 15x + 9) / (-4x - 3)", "answer": "-x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-4x - 3 | 4x^2 + 15x + 9\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(6x^3 + 7x^2 - 1) / (-3x + 1)", "answer": "-2x^2 - 3x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x + 1 | 6x^3 + 7x^2 - 1\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^2 - x + 2) / (-2x - 1)", "answer": "5x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x - 1 | -10x^2 - x + 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-x^3 + 4x^2 + 2x - 5) / (-x + 1)", "answer": "x^2 - 3x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x + 1 | -x^3 + 4x^2 + 2x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^3 + 19x^2 - 9) / (5x + 3)", "answer": "-2x^2 + 5x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x + 3 | -10x^3 + 19x^2 - 9\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^2 + 23x - 12) / (-2x + 3)", "answer": "5x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x + 3 | -10x^2 + 23x - 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-6x^3 + 11x^2 + x - 6) / (2x - 3)", "answer": "-3x^2 + x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n2x - 3 | -6x^3 + 11x^2 + x - 6\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(16x^3 - 12x^2 + 12x + 4) / (-4x - 1)", "answer": "-4x^2 + 4x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-4x - 1 | 16x^3 - 12x^2 + 12x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^2 + 4x + 4) / (4x + 2)", "answer": "-2x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x + 2 | -8x^2 + 4x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^3 - 22x^2 + 5x + 6) / (5x - 3)", "answer": "-x^2 - 5x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x - 3 | -5x^3 - 22x^2 + 5x + 6\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^3 + 2x + 3) / (-x + 1)", "answer": "5x^2 + 5x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x + 1 | -5x^3 + 2x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(20x^2 - 9x - 20) / (4x - 5)", "answer": "5x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x - 5 | 20x^2 - 9x - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(9x^2 - 12x - 5) / (3x + 1)", "answer": "3x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n3x + 1 | 9x^2 - 12x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(8x^3 - 6x^2 - x + 6) / (4x + 3)", "answer": "2x^2 - 3x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x + 3 | 8x^3 - 6x^2 - x + 6\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^3 - 22x^2 - 20x - 16) / (2x + 4)", "answer": "-4x^2 - 3x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n2x + 4 | -8x^3 - 22x^2 - 20x - 16\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^3 + 21x^2 + 24x - 20) / (x - 5)", "answer": "-5x^2 - 4x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\nx - 5 | -5x^3 + 21x^2 + 24x - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(5x^3 - 24x^2 + 15x + 4) / (x - 4)", "answer": "5x^2 - 4x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\nx - 4 | 5x^3 - 24x^2 + 15x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-15x^2 + 11x + 12) / (-3x + 4)", "answer": "5x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x + 4 | -15x^2 + 11x + 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-15x^3 + 17x^2 - 13x + 3) / (-3x + 1)", "answer": "5x^2 - 4x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x + 1 | -15x^3 + 17x^2 - 13x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(16x^3 - 4x^2 - 32x + 15) / (4x - 5)", "answer": "4x^2 + 4x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x - 5 | 16x^3 - 4x^2 - 32x + 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-6x^3 - 19x^2 - 21x - 9) / (-2x - 3)", "answer": "3x^2 + 5x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x - 3 | -6x^3 - 19x^2 - 21x - 9\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-2x^2 - 6x - 4) / (x + 1)", "answer": "-2x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\nx + 1 | -2x^2 - 6x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^2 + 3x - 15) / (-3x + 3)", "answer": "-4x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x + 3 | 12x^2 + 3x - 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-12x^3 + 31x^2 - 32x + 16) / (-3x + 4)", "answer": "4x^2 - 5x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x + 4 | -12x^3 + 31x^2 - 32x + 16\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^3 - 13x^2 + 4x + 4) / (-3x + 2)", "answer": "x^2 + 5x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x + 2 | -3x^3 - 13x^2 + 4x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-x^3 - 2x^2 + 10x - 4) / (x - 2)", "answer": "-x^2 - 4x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\nx - 2 | -x^3 - 2x^2 + 10x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^3 - x^2 - 3x + 3) / (-2x + 1)", "answer": "5x^2 + 3x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x + 1 | -10x^3 - x^2 - 3x + 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^3 + 12x^2 - 16) / (2x + 4)", "answer": "2x^2 + 2x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n2x + 4 | 4x^3 + 12x^2 - 16\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-20x^2 - 12x + 8) / (-4x - 4)", "answer": "5x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-4x - 4 | -20x^2 - 12x + 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-2x^2 - 9x - 10) / (-x - 2)", "answer": "2x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x - 2 | -2x^2 - 9x - 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^2 - 6x + 5) / (4x + 5)", "answer": "-2x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x + 5 | -8x^2 - 6x + 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^3 - x^2 + 8x - 4) / (x + 2)", "answer": "-3x^2 + 5x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\nx + 2 | -3x^3 - x^2 + 8x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(20x^2 + 17x - 10) / (-4x - 5)", "answer": "-5x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-4x - 5 | 20x^2 + 17x - 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(15x^2 - 10x - 25) / (5x + 5)", "answer": "3x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x + 5 | 15x^2 - 10x - 25\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(5x^3 + 25x^2 + 15x - 5) / (5x + 5)", "answer": "x^2 + 4x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x + 5 | 5x^3 + 25x^2 + 15x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(8x^3 + 12x^2 - 16x - 20) / (-4x - 4)", "answer": "-2x^2 - x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-4x - 4 | 8x^3 + 12x^2 - 16x - 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^2 + 11x - 3) / (-x - 3)", "answer": "-4x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x - 3 | 4x^2 + 11x - 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(15x^2 - 12x - 3) / (5x + 1)", "answer": "3x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x + 1 | 15x^2 - 12x - 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(8x^2 - 2) / (4x + 2)", "answer": "2x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x + 2 | 8x^2 - 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-3x^3 - 10x^2 + 16x + 15) / (-3x + 5)", "answer": "x^2 + 5x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-3x + 5 | -3x^3 - 10x^2 + 16x + 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-4x^2 - 10x - 4) / (-2x - 1)", "answer": "2x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x - 1 | -4x^2 - 10x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^3 - 3x^2 + 21x - 4) / (5x - 1)", "answer": "-2x^2 - x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x - 1 | -10x^3 - 3x^2 + 21x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-15x^3 + 7x^2 - 4x + 4) / (3x - 2)", "answer": "-5x^2 - x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n3x - 2 | -15x^3 + 7x^2 - 4x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^3 + 19x^2 + 24x + 4) / (5x + 1)", "answer": "-x^2 + 4x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x + 1 | -5x^3 + 19x^2 + 24x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-25x^2 + 5x + 2) / (5x + 1)", "answer": "-5x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x + 1 | -25x^2 + 5x + 2\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(x^2 - 7x + 10) / (-x + 2)", "answer": "-x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x + 2 | x^2 - 7x + 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^2 - x - 1) / (-4x - 1)", "answer": "-3x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-4x - 1 | 12x^2 - x - 1\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-20x^3 - 29x^2 + 20x + 5) / (5x + 1)", "answer": "-4x^2 - 5x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x + 1 | -20x^3 - 29x^2 + 20x + 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(12x^2 + 17x - 5) / (3x + 5)", "answer": "4x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n3x + 5 | 12x^2 + 17x - 5\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(20x^2 + 4x - 16) / (5x - 4)", "answer": "4x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x - 4 | 20x^2 + 4x - 16\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^3 + 5x^2 + 13x - 6) / (-x + 2)", "answer": "5x^2 + 5x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x + 2 | -5x^3 + 5x^2 + 13x - 6\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-20x^2 - 26x - 8) / (-5x - 4)", "answer": "4x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-5x - 4 | -20x^2 - 26x - 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(8x^3 - 10x^2 - 15x - 3) / (-4x - 1)", "answer": "-2x^2 + 3x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-4x - 1 | 8x^3 - 10x^2 - 15x - 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(x^3 + 4x^2 + 4x + 1) / (-x - 1)", "answer": "-x^2 - 3x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x - 1 | x^3 + 4x^2 + 4x + 1\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^3 + 6x^2 - 11x + 20) / (-4x + 5)", "answer": "2x^2 + x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-4x + 5 | -8x^3 + 6x^2 - 11x + 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^2 + 27x - 10) / (-5x + 2)", "answer": "x - 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-5x + 2 | -5x^2 + 27x - 10\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-8x^3 + 18x^2 - 14x + 20) / (-2x + 4)", "answer": "4x^2 - x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x + 4 | -8x^3 + 18x^2 - 14x + 20\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^2 + 10x + 6) / (-2x - 3)", "answer": "-2x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-2x - 3 | 4x^2 + 10x + 6\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(5x^2 + 14x + 8) / (-x - 2)", "answer": "-5x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x - 2 | 5x^2 + 14x + 8\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-5x^3 - 5x^2 - 15x + 25) / (-5x + 5)", "answer": "x^2 + 2x + 5", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-5x + 5 | -5x^3 - 5x^2 - 15x + 25\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(20x^3 + 9x^2 - 19x - 4) / (-5x - 1)", "answer": "-4x^2 - x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-5x - 1 | 20x^3 + 9x^2 - 19x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-10x^2 - 22x - 4) / (5x + 1)", "answer": "-2x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x + 1 | -10x^2 - 22x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-20x^3 - 5x^2 + 13x - 15) / (4x + 5)", "answer": "-5x^2 + 5x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x + 5 | -20x^3 - 5x^2 + 13x - 15\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^2 - 4) / (4x - 4)", "answer": "x + 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x - 4 | 4x^2 - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(2x^3 - 10x^2 + 9x - 4) / (-x + 4)", "answer": "-2x^2 + 2x - 1", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-x + 4 | 2x^3 - 10x^2 + 9x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(4x^2 - 10x + 4) / (4x - 2)", "answer": "x - 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x - 2 | 4x^2 - 10x + 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(8x^3 - 14x^2 + 15x - 3) / (4x - 1)", "answer": "2x^2 - 3x + 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x - 1 | 8x^3 - 14x^2 + 15x - 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-12x^3 - 17x^2 + 21x - 4) / (-4x + 1)", "answer": "3x^2 + 5x - 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n-4x + 1 | -12x^3 - 17x^2 + 21x - 4\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(3x^3 + 7x^2 - 4x + 6) / (x + 3)", "answer": "3x^2 - 2x + 2", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\nx + 3 | 3x^3 + 7x^2 - 4x + 6\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(15x^2 - 12x - 3) / (5x + 1)", "answer": "3x - 3", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n5x + 1 | 15x^2 - 12x - 3\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"},
  {"type": "text", "question": "Divide:\n(-4x^3 + 17x^2 + 31x + 12) / (4x + 3)", "answer": "-x^2 + 5x + 4", "explanation": "Begin by setting up a long division format with the first equation inside the bar and the second outside\n\n4x + 3 | -4x^3 + 17x^2 + 31x + 12\nThen find a term such that when multiplied by the first term of the second equation will equal the first term of the first equation\n"}
]}